Guide to the Sarah Dyer Zine Collection, 1985-2005 RL.01138
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Sarah Dyer Zine Collection, 1985-2005, 7 boxes
  - box 7 (Box 7)
    - Yeide (Box 7)
    - Yello' Girl (Box 7)
    - You Might As Well Live (Box 7)
    - You Start It All (Box 7)
    - Yum (Box 7)
    - Zenchiskiki (Box 7)
    - Zero (Box 7)
    - Zero Hour (Box 7)
    - Zine 26 (Box 7)
    - Ziplocked (Box 7)
    - Zugang (Box 7)
    - [Untitled] (Box 7)
    - [Miscellania] (Box 7)
    - Audio cassette tape: Justified Action (Box 7)
- Addition #1 (2002-0319), 3 boxes
  - Action Girl (Box 8)
  - Action Girl Guide (Box 8)
  - Action Girl Newsletter (Box 8)
  - Adventures of A-Girl (Box 8)
  - Aim (Box 8)
  - Aim Your Dick (Box 8)
  - Alice's Adventures in Wonderland (Box 8)
  - Alternator (Box 8)
  - Amaterasu (Box 8)
  - Art Babe (Box 8)
  - As Air to Water (Box 8)
  - Assassin and the Whiner (Box 8)
  - Beautiful Bras and Bodyhair (Box 8)
  - Beloved (Box 8)
  - Black Light Angels (Box 8)
  - Bloodletting (Box 8)
  - Bloody Wymmin (Box 8)
  - Blue Hole (Box 8)
  - Bonnie the Stalker (Box 8)
  - Boredom Suck (Box 8)
  - Boy (Box 8)
  - Bust (Box 8)
  - Butt-rash (Box 8)
  - Cakewalk (Box 8)
  - Calling (Box 8)
  - Catbox Room (Box 8)
  - Certifiable (Box 8)
  - Citronella (Box 8)
  - City Girl's Sweet Loves (Box 8)
  - Clique Clack (Box 8)
  - Cryptographer (Box 8)
  - Damned Bunnies (Box 8)
  - Damsel Fly (Box 8)
  - Dandelion (Box 8)
  - Deep Girl (Box 8)
  - Definition (Box 8)
  - Diva (Box 8)
  - Dodo Comix (Box 8)
  - Dust Is Settling As We Speak (Box 8)
  - Dyke's Delight (Box 8)
  - Eggplant (Box 8)
  - Eno Scent (Box 8)
  - Eroteticism (Box 8)
  - Estrus (Box 8)
  - Exhibit A (Box 8)
  - Fabulous Babes (Box 8)
  - Fem Power (Box 9A)
  - Flatter (Box 9A)
  - Fuel (Box 9A)
  - Geek Stuff for Girls (Box 9A)
  - Girl Frenzy (Box 9A)
  - Girl Hero (Box 9A)
  - Girl Wonder (Box 9A)
  - Girlieface (Box 9A)
  - Girltalk (Box 9A)
  - Gunslingers (Box 9A)
  - Halo (Box 9A)
  - Happy Zine (Box 9A)
  - Hopster's Tracks (Box 9A)
  - How Comics Can Change the World (Box 9A)
  - I am the Thumb Tack (Box 9A)
  - Iblot Under the Milk (Box 9A)
  - Igor in a Pink Angora Sweater (Box 9A)
  - I Love Shojo Manga (Box 9A)
  - Jennifer Daydreamer (Box 9A)
  - Kronikle Komix (Box 9A)
  - La Petite Harlequin (Box 9A)
  - Lemonade (Box 9A)
  - Library Bonnet (Box 9A)
  - Lil Rhino Gazette (Box 9A)
  - Liliane (Box 9A)
  - Loserville (Box 9A)
  - Lumpophilia (Box 9A)
  - Lyra (Box 9A)
  - Mad Planet (Box 9A)
  - Mama Dramas (Box 9A)
  - Manic Panic (Box 9A)
  - Mile Post One Eleven (Box 9A)
  - Moist (Amsterdam) (Box 9A)
  - Moist (Chicago) (Box 9A)
  - Mons of Venus (Box 9B)
  - Negative Buttheads (Box 9B)
  - Night Club (Box 9B)
  - Nocturnal Emissions (Box 9B)
  - OK Not OK (Box 9B)
  - Oya (Box 9B)
  - P & E Newsletter (Box 9B)
  - Pander Zine Distro (Box 9B)
  - Pandora's Box (Box 9B)
  - Paranoiac Gum (Box 9B)
  - Pasty (Box 9B)
  - Peinyce Invee (Box 9B)
  - Peri Peri Thang (Box 9B)
  - Perky's Simo (Box 9B)
  - Pocket (Box 9B)
  - Posthumous (Box 9B)
  - Potential (Box 9B)
  - Pout (Box 9B)
  - Power Candy (Box 9B)
  - Pox (Box 9B)
  - Pretty Beaver (Box 9B)
  - Psychobitch (Box 9B)
  - Racecar Magazine (Box 9B)
  - Rage Doll (Box 9B)
  - Raspberry (Box 9B)
  - Red-Hooded Sweatshirt (Box 9B)
  - Riotemptresses (Box 9B)
  - Repressed in Portland (Box 9B)
  - Resist Psychic Death (Box 9B)
  - Rivets Hold the World Together (Box 9B)
  - Roadside (Box 9B)
  - Septophilia Mail Order (Box 9B)
  - She God (Box 9B)
  - She Wrinkles (Box 9B)
  - Skeleton Girl Comics (Box 9B)
  - Skim Lizard (Box 9B)
  - Smoking Devil (Box 10)
  - Spilt Milk (Box 10)
  - Stained Pages (Box 10)
  - Starache (Box 10)
  - Sugar Baby Bunting (Box 10)
  - Super Witch (Box 10)
  - Suva- Big Smoke- Fiji (Box 10)
  - Tabletop (Box 10)
  - Ten Suggestions (Box 10)
  - This is God's Zine (Box 10)
  - Thrift Score (Box 10)
  - Tomato (Box 10)
  - Totally Socially Unacceptable Alphabet (Box 10)
  - Tough Love (Box 10)
  - Twat (Box 10)
  - Vivid (Box 10)
  - We Love Food (Box 10)
  - Wide Arsed Mole (Box 10)
  - Wimmin's Comix (Box 10)
  - Women's Music Plus Directory (Box 10)
  - World War 3 (Box 10)
  - Yard Wide Yarns (Box 10)
  - Zero Hour (Box 10)
  - Zine Reviews (Box 10)
  - Zoey's Desk (Box 10)
  - 3 audiocassettes (Box 10)
  - 1 VHS tape (Box 10)
- Addition #2 (2006-0068), 6 boxes
  - Women-authored
    - A-Girl Is Swanky! (Box 11)
    - Ab Imo Pectore (Box 11)
    - Ab Inspector (Box 11)
    - The Accolade (Box 11)
    - Adventures of A-Girl! (Box 11)
    - Aim Comics (Box 11)
    - Amaranta (Box 11)
    - Animal Party (Box 11)
    - Anti-Social Commentary (Box 11)
    - Anything But Ordinary (Box 11)
    - Art Babe (Box 11)
    - Asking For It (Box 11)
    - The Assassin and the Whiner (Box 11)
    - Awkward (Box 11)
    - Bamboo Girl (Box 11)
    - Bejeezus (Box 11)
    - Bathroom Girls (Box 11)
    - Bored in School (Box 11)
    - Catfight (Box 11)
    - Chinchilla (Box 11)
    - Coagulate Comics (Box 11)
    - Cookie (Box 11)
    - Custard King (Box 11)
    - Dear Sister George: (Box 11)
    - Deep Girl (Box 11)
    - Dementa Praecox (Box 11)
    - Do You Remember Yvette? (Box 11)
    - Dolltopia (Box 11)
    - Dork Lifestyle (Box 11)
    - Driving Home (Box 11)
    - Dumb Luck (Box 11)
    - Duty Must Be Done (Box 11)
    - Elizabeth's Pritty Pictures Book (Box 11)
    - Freckles! (Box 11)
    - Fuzzy Heads Are Better (Box 11)
    - Girl Frenzy (Box 11)
    - Girl Stories (Box 11)
    - Girlhero (Box 11)
    - Girls World (Box 11)
    - Gotho the Clown and the Necro Freakshow (Box 12)
    - Help, My Snowman's Burning (Box 12)
    - How Comics Can Change the World! (Box 12)
    - Hyperventilate (Box 12)
    - I Didn't Ask for Any of This!! (Box 12)
    - I'm So Happy Today I Found My Friends (Box 12)
    - Indie Rock 2 tha Max (Box 12)
    - Into the Elephant Belly (Box 12)
    - I've been walking after midnight searching for you... (Box 12)
    - Jennifer Daydreamer (Box 12)
    - Julio's Brother Juan (Box 12)
    - Just a Guy (Box 12)
    - Kneehigh (Box 12)
    - The Koi Fish (Box 12)
    - Kronikle Komix (Box 12)
    - Last Call (Box 12)
    - Le Petite Harlequin (Box 12)
    - Lesbian Contradiction (Box 12)
    - Liliane (Box 12)
    - Lively Mud (Box 12)
    - Living Doll Disaster (Box 12)
    - Looking Back (Box 12)
    - Lyra (Box 12)
    - MelissaZine (Box 12)
    - Minimum Security (Box 12)
    - Miracle: A Short Story (Box 12)
    - Misery & Vomit (Box 12)
    - Mitten Brain (Box 12)
    - My Body Is a Glorious Manifestation of Nature... (Box 12)
    - My Brain Hurts (Box 12)
    - Nerve (Box 12)
    - Nice (Box 12)
    - OH (Box 12)
    - Panophobia (Box 12)
    - Paper Stars (Box 12)
    - Pocket Rocket (Box 12)
    - Power to Express: Passion (Box 12)
    - The Private Eye (Box 12)
    - Puke Junk and Hit the Fan (Box 12)
    - Pussy (Box 12)
    - Queen of Swords (Box 12)
    - Quick Comix (Box 12)
    - Rejected (Box 12)
    - Rock Candy (Box 12)
    - Rock, Paper, Scissors (Box 12)
    - Rollerderby (Box 12)
    - Seattle Trash (Box 13)
    - Sioux's Subversive Fables (Box 13)
    - Something Perfect (Box 13)
    - Super Vagina (Box 13)
    - Tequilla With Lime (Box 13)
    - That Girl (Box 13)
    - That Thing You Fall Into (Box 13)
    - This Is Your Toy and I Want It (Box 13)
    - Three-Way Kill-Time (Box 13)
    - To Avoid Suffocation (Box 13)
    - Tommy X-Ray and the Sympathy Fucks (Box 13)
    - Total Disaster! (Box 13)
    - Tough Love (Box 13)
    - Trinity (Box 13)
    - True! Wedding Funnies (Box 13)
    - Twat! (Box 13)
    - Ugly Mug (Box 13)
    - Underbelly Comics (Box 13)
    - Very Nice Gravy (Box 13)
    - Vox (Box 13)
    - West Star Land (Box 13)
    - Where's a Cookie (Box 13)
    - Why We Live (Box 13)
    - Wilnot (Box 13)
    - Writing Love Letters to Your Pants (Box 13)
    - Yeah It Is! (Box 13)
    - Yoohoo Haiku! (Box 13)
    - Zero Hour (Box 13)
    - Riot Grrrl (t-shirt) (Box 13)
    - Rock 'n Roll Jamboree (VHS) (Box 13)
  - Male-authored
    - 9-11 (Box 14)
    - Abraxia's Dream (Box 14)
    - Ain't Nothin' Like Fuckin' Moonshine (Box 14)
    - Beer Frame: The Journal of Inconspicuous Consumption (Box 14)
    - Boy Trouble (Box 14)
    - Chic-A-Go-Go (Box 14)
    - Circus Fiasco (Box 14)
    - Colin's Comics (Box 14)
    - Cometbus (Box 14)
    - Comet Debris (Box 14)
    - Compendium (Box 14)
    - Confessions of a Tabletop General (Box 14)
    - Dead Men's Tales (Box 14)
    - Dear Rocket Records (Box 14)
    - Drunken Master (Box 14)
    - Drunken Master 2 (Box 14)
    - Flukes (Box 14)
    - Flytrap (Box 14)
    - Giant Robot (Box 14)
    - Ha Ha Magazine (Box 14)
    - Heinous (Box 14)
    - Insurgence Magazine (Box 14)
    - (Joshua Sullivan) (Box 14)
    - Kitschy Kitschy Coup (Box 14)
    - The Last Prom (Box 14)
    - Little White Bird (Box 14)
    - Macros 2000 (Box 14)
    - Mighty Fine (Box 14)
    - A Modern World (Box 14)
    - Monorail (Box 14)
    - Morgana von Barron Goth Weathergirl (Box 14)
    - The Nosebleed Section (Box 14)
    - Oscar Chavez...Machismo Monitor! (Box 14)
    - Punk Planet (Box 14)
    - Roctober (Box 14)
    - Roctober (continued) (Box 15)
    - Senses (Box 16)
    - Stewart Kimura Feels No Pain (Box 16)
    - The Stockboy (Box 16)
    - That Skinny Bastard (Box 16)
    - Thrill (Box 16)
    - Tiki News (Box 16)
    - Truthseekers Guide to the Magic Kingdom (Box 16)
    - TV Grind (Box 16)
    - Viper Press Presents (Box 16)
    - The Walking Man (Box 16)
    - Words & Pictures (Box 16)
- Addition #3 (2008-0030), 4 boxes
  - Action Girl Minizine (Box 17)
  - Action Girl Newsletter (Box 17)
  - Algernon (Box 17)
  - Alice the Camel (Box 17)
  - Attack! (Box 17)
  - Ball Peen Comics (Box 17)
  - Bean Dip (Box 17)
  - Bedtime Stories for Trivial Teens (Box 17)
  - Bellybutton Explosion (Box 17)
  - Bellyflop (Box 17)
  - Blue Roses (Box 17)
  - Bomb (Box 17)
  - Book of Days (Box 17)
  - Boredom Sucks (Box 17)
  - Brain Spa (Box 17)
  - Brassy Grrrl Newsletter (Box 17)
  - Busboy (Box 17)
  - Ceilings Peel (Box 17)
  - Certifiable (Box 17)
  - C'est La Vie (Box 17)
  - Cheese Log (Box 17)
  - Children Who Sit Alone at Lunch (Box 17)
  - Chum (Box 17)
  - Clique Clack (Box 17)
  - Clitoris (Box 17)
  - Crazy Daisy (Box 17)
  - Crème Brulee (Box 17)
  - Cubbyhole (Box 17)
  - Cupsize (Box 17)
  - Design (Box 17)
  - Die Right Now (Box 17)
  - Disarm (Box 17)
  - Don't Even (Box 17)
  - Duhhh (Box 17)
  - Eel (Box 17)
  - Emily Lives Alone (Box 17)
  - Every Girl's Dream (Box 17)
  - Family Next Door (Box 17)
  - Feeding the Fouls (Box 17)
  - Femme Flicke (Box 17)
  - First Time (Box 17)
  - Forks and Attitudes (Box 17)
  - Fragments (Box 17)
  - Fuck Off and Die (Box 17)
  - Function (Box 17)
  - Fussbudget (Box 17)
  - Girl Cola (Box 17)
  - Girl Label Directory (Box 17)
  - Girl Trouble (Box 17)
  - Griselda (Box 17)
  - Grope (Box 17)
  - Grot Grrrl (Box 17)
  - Gumshoe (Box 17)
  - Habitual Freak (Box 18)
  - Hazmat (Box 18)
  - Hell Cat (Box 18)
  - Hell Kitty (Box 18)
  - Hey Gurly (Box 18)
  - Hip Mama (Box 18)
  - Hissyfitt (Box 18)
  - Hodge Podge (Box 18)
  - I Hate You (Box 18)
  - I Liked Betty (Box 18)
  - I Rule (Box 18)
  - Iblot Under the Milk (Box 18)
  - I'm So Fucking Beautiful (Box 18)
  - Impress Your Friends (Box 18)
  - Information Panic (Box 18)
  - Ivy's Poop (Box 18)
  - Jellybean (Box 18)
  - Jungle Gym (Box 18)
  - Just Fine (Box 18)
  - Ketchup (Box 18)
  - Kitty Nip (Box 18)
  - Ladybird (Box 18)
  - Lesbian Contradiction (Box 18)
  - Lime Green News (Box 18)
  - Linda (Box 18)
  - Loud As Hell (Box 18)
  - Lull (Box 18)
  - Marika (Box 18)
  - Marmalade (Box 18)
  - Me First (Box 18)
  - Milkweed (Box 18)
  - Miss Michigan (Box 18)
  - Mold (Box 18)
  - Mouse Soup (Box 18)
  - Ms America (Box 18)
  - Muffinbones (Box 18)
  - My Last Nerve (Box 18)
  - My Zine (Box 18)
  - Nerd Girl (Box 18)
  - OH (Box 18)
  - Outhouse (Box 18)
  - Out of the Vortex (Box 18)
  - Oya (Box 18)
  - Panik (Box 18)
  - Panophobia (Box 18)
  - Pawholes (Box 18)
  - Peach (Box 18)
  - Pesky Meddling Girls (Box 19)
  - Pinkus Blank (Box 19)
  - Placebo (Box 19)
  - Plan Your Work (Box 19)
  - Power Candy (Box 19)
  - Pretty Mess (Box 19)
  - Private Catholic (Box 19)
  - Progress Sucks (Box 19)
  - Pussy Cat Vision (Box 19)
  - Queenie (Box 19)
  - Rag (Box 19)
  - Raspberry (Box 19)
  - Riot Grrrl Olympia (Box 19)
  - Riot Grrrl Press (Box 19)
  - Roller Derby (Box 19)
  - Runt (Box 19)
  - Sad (Box 19)
  - Scorpio Girl's Revenge (Box 19)
  - Secret Weapon (Box 19)
  - Sheep in America (Box 19)
  - She God (Box 19)
  - Simba (Box 19)
  - Skew (Box 19)
  - Slug and Lettuce (Box 19)
  - Slumber (Box 19)
  - Soldiers Without Guns (Box 19)
  - Sour Puss (Box 19)
  - Space Craft Convention (Box 19)
  - Spit (Box 19)
  - Spludge (Box 19)
  - Standard Deviation (Box 19)
  - Straight and Narrow (Box 19)
  - Stumble (Box 19)
  - Survival Guide for Her Repellant (Box 19)
  - Sweet Heart (Box 19)
  - Teenage Whore Book (Box 19)
  - Thrift Score (Box 19)
  - Twelve (Box 19)
  - Umbrella Stand (Box 19)
  - Unclean (Box 19)
  - Viridescence (Box 19)
  - Wandromedia (Box 19)
  - William Wants a Doll (Box 19)
  - W.I.C.C.A. (Box 19)
  - Womyn Who Masturbate (Box 19)
  - Yellow Curtain (Box 19)
  - Y is for Yuck (Box 19)
  - Yum (Box 19)
  - Zine Ephemera (Box 19)
  - Broad Humor (Box 20)
  - Captain Howdy (Box 20)
  - Caption (Box 20)
  - Charm School (Box 20)
  - Choices (Box 20)
  - Clarkson (Box 20)
  - Dale Messick Cut-outs and Coloring Book (Box 20)
  - Deadsy Cat + Kissy Kat (Box 20)
  - Flim Flam (Box 20)
  - Fusion/Translucid Distortion (Box 20)
  - Girl Frenzy Millennial (Box 20)
  - Girlyhead (Box 20)
  - i was 7 in '75 (Box 20)
  - Idiosyncrasy (Box 20)
  - Katy and Gloria in Meow Meow Paper Doll Book (Box 20)
  - Katy Keene Paper Doll Book (Box 20)
  - Miss Fury (Box 20)
  - Pale Fire (Box 20)
  - Paper Dolls from the Comics (Box 20)
  - Phone Call (Box 20)
  - Return of the Pez-Eaters (Box 20)
  - Tin House (Box 20)
  - Turpentine (Box 20)
  - two become one (Box 20)
  - Whores of mensa (Box 20)
  - Wimmen's (Box 20)
  - zine scene from Entertainment Tonight (VHS tape) (Box 20)